https://www.trinitybiotech.com/privacy-statement/

Location:
News & Events
Location:
Privacy Statement
We at Trinity Biotech understand that privacy protection is of utmost importance. We recognise that certain standards of personal data privacy exist and guarantee that we will meet and surpass these standards to the greatest extent possible. Consequently we invite you to read our privacy statement, so you are aware of and understand our privacy measures.
Data Collection
We do not require you to provide us with any personal information, except when you request a product or service via our web-site. Information collected maybe used for administrative purposes, internal marketing or for other purposes which may contribute to the development or enhancement of our web-site. This data will not be sold, rented or dispersed to any other party unless the end user has agreed to its distribution. We may however use information at the request of any government body or legal entity, which may involve identifying an individual. When forwarding communications, a product or service, we will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.
Personal data collection and processing
Information is only collected when it is provided to us by you, through e-mails, order forms, inquiries, registration and other situations where you are choosing to provide us with personal information.
Your personal information will be used only by Trinity Biotech Plc. and third parties affiliates. Personal data will not be distributed by us or by those acting for us under any circumstance other that with your consent or due to legal requirements.
Purpose of Use
When information is collected we use it to allow us to supply you with requested products or service and for any reason permitted by law. You may be asked in certain areas of the web-site to specify your preference as whether you wish to receive information and/or promotional material regarding Trinity Biotech Plc. and/or third parties with whom we have a strategic business relationship with. We respect such preference and you have the entitlement to change such a preference in accordance with the “Right of Cancellation” section below.
Right of Cancellation
At anytime you have the right to withdraw your consent for the use of your personal data in the future, includes receipt of information and/or promotional material from our company and associated third parties. To exercise this right, please simply contact us at info@trinitybiotech.com.
Right of Access and Correction
At anytime you have the right to amend or review any of your personal data that we have collected if you believe it to be inaccurate or out of date. To do so please contact us at info@trinitybiotech.com.
Contacts
The constant development of the Internet requires occasional alteration to our privacy statement. We retain the right to make changes when required. If you have any queries regarding our website please do not hesitate to contact us at info@trinitybiotech.com.
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However you may visit Cookie Settings to provide a controlled consent. Privacy Policy Cookie settingsREJECT ACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
CookieTypeDurationDescriptionfpestid01 yearFpestid is a ShareThis cookie ID set in the domain of the website operator.localesession1 monthUsed by the site to show content to users based on their selected location._ga02 yearsThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, camapign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assigns a randoly generated number to identify unique visitors._gat01 minuteThis cookies is installed by Google Universal Analytics to throttle the request rate to limit the colllection of data on high traffic sites._gid01 dayThis cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the wbsite is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages viisted in an anonymous form._hrmts_locationString1Unclassified 3rd party cookie used by the HR Manager service	__stid01 yearThe cookie is set by ShareThis. The cookie is used for site analytics to determine the pages visited, the amount of time spent, etc.__stidv01 yearThe cookie is set by ShareThis. The cookie is used for site analytics to determine the pages visited, the amount of time spent, etc.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non Necessary
non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Analytics
analytics
Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.
Performance
performance
Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.
Necessary
necessary-2
Save & Accept
Choose Location
Global - Non USA/Canada
USA
Canada
